{
  "data": [
    {
      "answer": "x = 3 \n for i in range(x): \n\t print(i) \n # Output: \n 1 \n 2 \n 3",
      "question": "create for loop"
    },
    {
      "answer": "def function(): \n \t pass",
      "question": "create function"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_variable = \"Hello World\"",
      "question": "create variable"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_list = [\"Hello\",\"World\"]",
      "question": "create list"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_list = [\"Hello\",\"World\"] \n print(my_list[0]) \n print(my_list[1] \n # Output: \n Hello \n World",
      "question": "print an element from a list"
    },
    {
      "answer": "def function({x}):\n \t pass",
      "question": "create function with parameter {x}"
    },
    {
      "answer": "file = open('filename.txt').read().split(\"\\n\") \n print(file)",
      "question": "save every single line of a file into a list"
    },
    {
      "answer": "with open('filename.txt', 'w') as f: \n \t f.write('Hello World!')",
      "question": "write into a file"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_list = [\"Hello\"] \n my_list.append(\"World\") \n print(my_list) \n# Output: [\"Hello\", \"World\"]",
      "question": "append an element to a list"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_list = [\"Hello\", \"World\"] \n for element in my_list: \n \t print(element) \n # Output: Hello, World",
      "question": "loop through a list and print each element"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_dict = {\"key1\": \"value1\", \"key2\": \"value2\"} \n print(my_dict) \n # Output: {\"key1\": \"value1\", \"key2\": \"value2\"}",
      "question": "create a dictonary"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_dict = {\"key1\": \"value1\", \"key2\": \"value2\"} \n value = my_dict[\"key1\"] \n print(value) \n # Output: value1",
      "question": "get an element from a dictonary"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_dict = {'a': 1, 'b': 2} \n my_dict['c'] = 3 \n \nprint(my_dict)",
      "question": "add a new key-value pair to a dictionary"
    },
    {
      "answer": "class MyClass: \n \t def __init__(self): \t \t self.my_variable = \"Hello World\" \n my_object = MyClass() \n print(my_object.my_variable) \n # Output: Hello World",
      "question": "create a class"
    },
    {
      "answer": "import math \\n result = math.sqrt(16) \\n print(result) \\n # Output: 4.0",
      "question": "import a module"
    },
    {
      "answer": "import pandas as pd \n # Create a DataFrame \n data = {'Name': ['John', 'Jane', 'Jack', 'Jill'], \n \t 'Age': [23, 25, 21, 18], \n \t 'Gender': ['M', 'F', 'M', 'F']} \n df = pd.DataFrame(data) \n # print DataFrame \n print(df)",
      "question": "create a dataframe"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_set = {1, 2, 3} \n my_set.add(4) \n \n print(my_set)",
      "question": "add a new element to a Python set"
    },
    {
      "answer": "df = pd.DataFrame({\"Name\": [\"Alice\", \"Bob\", \"Charlie\", \"Dave\", \"Eve\"], \n \t \"Age\": [25, 30, 30, 40, 45], \n \t\"Gender\": [\"F\", \"M\", \"M\", \"M\", \"F\"]}) \n selected_columns = df[[\"Name\", \"Age\"]] \n print(selected_columns)",
      "question": "select specific columns of a dataframe"
    },
    {
      "answer": "import pandas as pd \n # Create a dataframe with names and ages \n  df = pd.DataFrame({'Name': ['Alice', 'Bob', 'Charlie', 'Debbie'], \n \t 'Age': [25, 30, 35, 40]}) \n # Print the age of the person at row 2 \n print(df.at[2, 'Age'])",
      "question": "print a specific positon of a dataframe"
    },
    {
      "answer": "import pandas as pd \n \n # Create a dataframe with names and ages \n df = pd.DataFrame({'Name': ['Alice', 'Bob', 'Charlie', 'Debbie'],\n \t 'Age': [25, 30, 35, 40]}) \n # Set the index to be the 'Name' column \n df.set_index('Name', inplace=True) \n \n # Print the age of the person with name 'Charlie' \n print(df.at['Charlie', 'Age'])",
      "question": "print a specific positon of a dataframe clearly"
    },
    {
      "answer": "print(\"Hello World!\") \n # Output: Hello World!",
      "question": "print"
    },
    {
      "answer": "dict = {a\": 1,\"b\":2,\"c\":3} \n swapped_dictionary = {value: key for key, value in dict.items()|} \n #Output: \n {1: 'a', 2: 'b', 3: 'c'}",
      "question": "how can i swapp the values with the keys in a dictonary"
    },
    {
      "answer": "d = {'a': 1, 'b': 2, 'c': 3} \n values = my_dict.values() \n values_list = list(values) \n print(values_list)",
      "question": "How to get all values from a dictonary"
    },
    {
      "answer": "my_list = [1, 2, 3, 4, 2]\nfor item in my_list:\n\tif my_list.count(item) > 1:\n\tprint(f'{item} ist double')",
      "question": "get doubles from list"
    }
  ]
}